

NGUYEN DINH DUNG

Intern .net

30/07/2003

0358215597

dungnguyendev2k3@gmail.com

Nam Tu Liem District - Hanoi

Skill

Frontend: Angular js, HTML, CSS ,Bootstrap,JS



BackEnd:C#,OOP,Ajax,Window Form, SQL Server.







Framework:Fluent API,MVC,.Net Core, RESTfulAPI.







English level: Read and understand specialized language and communicate in basic English









Soft skills

Communication skills, learning skills, presentation skills, teamwork skills

TITLES AND AWARDS

6/7 semesters achieved the title of Good and Excellent student

OBJECTIVE

Short-term goal: Become an official employee after 2-3 months of internship, accumulate more experience in the Software field, practice effective work handling skills.

Long-term goal: Become a Senior Developer after 3-4 years of work. Create many quality products, contribute and stay long-term with the company

EDUCATION

08/2021 - 01/2024

FPT POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE |

Major: Software development /C# programming language

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2023 - 12/2023

GRADUATE PROJECT | Build a website selling SUPER-FASHION men's sportswear Main functions:

- Decentralize Admin, employee, customer, login and registration rights, user management.
- Product management, online sales, over-the-counter sales, online payment by VNPay, shipping fee calculation by GHN.
- · Manage promotion codes and statistics.

Work description:

• Design the database with the team, perform the function of decentralizing Admin, Employees, Customers, log in, register, forget password, change password, manage customers, employees, CRUD customers and employees, records my profile. Send order information emails to customers, build interfaces

Technology used:

 Used Entity Framework, ASP.NET Core Web API, ASP.NET Core Web App (MVC), Ajax, SQL, JWT, Mailkit.

Tools used:

 Used:SQL Server management studio, Visual Studio, Github desktop, Diagram.net, Postman, Swagger Ul.

Result

- · Learn a lot of new knowledge
- The project was highly appreciated and performed properly

LinkGitHub: https://github.com/DungNguyenCode/DATN

07/2023 - 08/2023

PERSONAL PROJECT | Build a website to sell phones

Main functions:

- Decentralize Admin, employee, customer, login and registration rights, user management.
- · Cart management, user management, product CRUD.

Work description:

• execute all functional flows, database design.

Technology used:

Used Entity Framework, ASP.NET Core Web API, ASP.NET Core Web App (MVC), Ajax, SQL.

· Used:SQL Server management studio, Visual Studio, Github desktop, Diagram.net, Postman, Swagger UI.

Result

Learn a lot of new knowledge

LinkGitHub:https://github.com/DungNguyenCode/ShopPhone_1.0